Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1950-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Arena Stage production correspondence, 1950-2000; 13.65 linear ft. (18 boxes)
  - A Perfect Ganesh (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - The Plough and the Stars (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - The Price (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Kiss me Kate (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - The Little Prince (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Long Days Journey into Night (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Love Letters Benefit (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Lovers and Executioners (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Matchmaker (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Misalliance (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - She Miser (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - The House of Martin Guerre (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Hysteria (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - I Am a Man (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - I'd Rather be Right (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - In the Deep Hearts Core (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Ain't Nothin but the Blues (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - It's the Truth (if you think it is) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Jar the Floor (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Jelly Roll (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - John Gabriel Borkman (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Journey to the West (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - June Moon (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - general correspondence "A" (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - general correspondence "B", 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - general correspondence "B", 2 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - general correspondence "C" (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - general correspondence "D", 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - general correspondence "D", 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - general correspondence "E" (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - general correspondence "F" (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - general correspondence "G" (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - general correspondence "H" (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - general correspondence "I-J" (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - general correspondence "K" (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - general correspondence "L" (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - general correspondence "M" (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - general correspondence "N" (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - General correspondence "O" (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - general correspondence "P-Q" (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - general correspondence "R" (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - general correspondence "S" (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - general correspondence "T" (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - general correspondence "U-V" (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - general correspondence "W" (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - general correspondence "X,Y,,Z" (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - contribution information 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - affirmative action and misc. items (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - D.C. public schools contract info (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Youth Awarness Program (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - community service project reconciliations 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - community service project 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Community service project 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - community service project 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - community service proposal 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - community service project general info (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - misc. bills (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - transcript of Robert Alexander at American University (Box 6A, Folder 1)
  - Living Stage / U. of Michigan (Box 6A, Folder 2)
  - Van American Foundation (Box 6A, Folder 3)
  - City Museum Project 1979 (Box 6A, Folder 4)
  - Internships (Box 6A, Folder 5)
  - Tiber Island (Box 6A, Folder 6)
  - Fedapt resources (Box 6A, Folder 7)
  - rewrites (Box 6A, Folder 8)
  - Space P.R. (Box 6A, Folder 9)
  - Notes (Box 6A, Folder 10)
  - correspondence, Cathy Irwin (Box 6A, Folder 11)
  - budget (Box 6A, Folder 12)
  - DOE proposal draft 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - addresses of supporters (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ballou Evaluation 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Audit (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - brown bag lunch programs (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - relationships (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - young audience (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - peace (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - bob's papers on self (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - RAD (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - D.C. humanities (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - suggestions (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - current addresses (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - misc. Living Stage info (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Living Stage info (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - associate letter (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - special proposal (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Frank Hodsoll, NEA (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - American Arts Alliance (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - TCG annual report (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Nabil Sawelka (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Elspeth Udvarhelyi (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - misc. correspondence (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - DOE proposal 1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - DOE proposal draft 1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Susan and Michael Samuels (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - fundraising (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Ballou H.S. evaluation (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - CSP evaluation 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - D.C. jail evaluation for women 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - D.C. jail evaluations 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - evaluations 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - evaluations 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - evaluations 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Evaluations 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Learning Stage Arena (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - DOE 1988 appendix (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - DOE proposals 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - contact sheets, 1 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - contact sheets, 2 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - contact sheets, 3 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - misc. memos and correspondence, July/December 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - misc. memos and correspondence, April - June 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Reading file Jan. - March 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - reading file - Oct. - Dec. 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - reading file - July-Sept. 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - reading file - April - June 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - reading file - March 1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - reading file - Jan. - Feb.1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - reading file - Sept. - Dec. 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Staff Meeting minutes 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - staff meeting minutes 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - staff meeting minutes 1986-1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - ontact sheets - 1970's (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - reading files special events (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - reading files / special events (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - reading files / special events (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - reading files / special events (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 2nd copy (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - staff meeting minutes (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - correspondence to "leaders and specialists" (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - reading file Jan. - May 1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - March 20th 1991 recpetion for Zelda Fichandler (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 40th anniversary - lists and memos (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 40th anniversary meetings (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - george's photo exhibit (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 40th anniversary - chairman letters (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - book - Death of a Salesmen, text and criticism (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Democracy and Esther, correspondence (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Days of our Life, correspondence (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Dead End Kids, handout (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Dedan Kimathi, text and correspondence (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Death of a Salesman, misc production material (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Death of a Salesman, misc. materials (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Death of a Salesman, Zelda's director's book (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - A Delicate Balence, misc. materials (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - A Delicate Balance, misc. info (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Mister Johnson, correspondence (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Miss Maragarida's Way (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Miss Julie, program (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Miss Ever's Boys (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The Misanthrope, program and review (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - A Midsummers Night's Dream, misc. production materials (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Mother of Courage, misc. materials (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Morning's at Seven, program (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Moon on a Rainbow Shawl, correspondence (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - A Moon for the Misbegotten, program and correspondence (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Morocco, script (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Moonchildren / Cancer, misc. correspondence and materials (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - The Mousetrap, program (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Mrs. Murray's Farm, program (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Mourning Becomes Electra, reviews (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Motel, script (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Mrs. Klein, misc. materials (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Medal of Honor Rag - program (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Mecca - correspondence (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Measure for Measure - script, press release, notes (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - The Matchmaker - program and notes (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Master Harold - script, program, notes (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mastergate - press clippings (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Men in White - program (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - A Memory of 2 Mondays - program, press clips (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - A Man's a Man - program, news release (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Mandragola - press release (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - The Man with a Load of Mischief - program, press release (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Man with a Raincoat - script, notes (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Man witha Raincoat - Playlab (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Marie and Bruce - program (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Marching Song - program (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - March of the Falsetts - press clippings (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - The Marathon - correspondence (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Marat / Sade - program (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom - program (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - A Map of the World - program and correspondence (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Master and Margarita - program, correspondence (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - The Master Builder - program (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Mass Appeal - program (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Mary Stuart - program, news clipping (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Mary Barnes - news clippings (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Marvin's Room - program (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Marry me a Little - program (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - The Marriage of Bette and Boo - program (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Melon - correspondence (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream - news clippings (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream - misc. notes (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - A Month in the Country - press clips (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Monoploy - showcase (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Money - correspondence, news clips (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - The Molly Maguires - programs (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Moliere in Spite of Himself - program (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Modigliani - press prints (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Moby Dick - program (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Much Ado About Nothing - program (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession - program (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Moxie Malone - correspondence, script, misc. notes (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Stephen Sondheim - press clips (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - George Furth - misc. notes (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Merrily We Roll Along - press clippings (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Merton of the Movies (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Arena Stage production contracts, 1950-2000; 2.25 linear ft. (4 boxes)
  Collection contains the production contracts and information for the Arena Stage.
  - Crime and Punishment 86/87 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yuri Lyubimov (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Piggy Bank 86/87 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Measure for Measure (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Marriage of bette and Boo 86/87 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Flying Karamazov Brothers 86/87 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Beehive 86/87 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Challegne Grant 90-94 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Endowment Camp 85/86 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Capital Needs List (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ourselves Alone 86/87 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Glengarry Glen Ross (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - All the King's Men 87/88 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Joe Turner's Come and Gone 87/88 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Immigrant 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - NEA / Richard Willbur tribute 3/88 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Light up the Sky 87/88 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American Splendor (stage four) 87/88 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Zeisler Award 86/87 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - American Theatre Season, The Crucible 87/88 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Crucible 86/87 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American Theater Season (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Late Great Labies of Blues and Jazz, '87 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Creative Programs/Dennis Doran 1/87 - 4/87 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Heartbreak House 86/87 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Asti Sponsored Soviet Designer visit 5/88 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Arena Tour 1986-1987 (Israel) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - NEA playwright in Residence 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gang of Five 85/86 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Enrico IV 87/88 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Les Blancs 87/88 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Checkmate (stage four) 87/88 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Janice F. Hill (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Cherry Orchard 87/88 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bill Stewart Stamp Award (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - A Chorus of Disapproval 1/89 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Briar Patch (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Playboy of the West Indies (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 6 Characttes in Search of an Author (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Ring Around the Moon (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - An Acting Workshop (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Abyssinia (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Suzaki / Lear (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Cocoanuts (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Judevine (stage 4), May 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - On The Town, April 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Nothing Sacred, March 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Lie of the Mind, March 1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Fool Show (Geoff hoyle) Feb. 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Senior Staff meeting minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Senior Staff meeting minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1995-1996 senior staff meeting minutes (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - A Walk in the Woods, symposium June, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A Walk in the Woods, June 1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Union tour 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Merrily We Roll Along, January 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Man Who Came to Dinner 11/1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - The Glass Menagerie 10/89 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - A Midsummers Night's Dream 9/89 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Stand-Up Tragedy 1/90 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Born Guilty, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Juno and the Paycock 5/90 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Fences 4/90 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Conquest of the SOuth Pole 3/90 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - A Doll House 3/90 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Closer Than Ever (book-in) 9/90 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - The Seagull 5/91 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Two gentelmen of Verona 5/91 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Vivisections from the Blown Mind 4/91 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - She Stoops to Conquer 3/91 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - My Childeren, My Africa! 1/91 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Pygmalion 2/91 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Born Guilty 1/91 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - From the Mississippi Delta 12/90 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Our Town 11/90 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cerceau 10/90 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle 9/90 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Grants and Contributions 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Grants and Contributions 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Grants 1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Grants and Contributions (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fine Commission 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NEH 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Grant 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - MUS appl. 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NEA: opera musical theater program 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fine Arts Commission 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - DC Commission (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Arena Stage production notebooks and programs, 1950-1991; 69 linear ft. (138 boxes)
  Production notebooks and programs for Arena Stage productions from 1950 to 1991. Notebooks contain playscripts, music and light cues, wardrobe, prop, notes, and stage-related information.
  - Abyssinia (Folder 1-3, Box 1)
  - Accidental Death (Folder 4-5, Box 1)
  - Adding Machine- A Play in Seven Scenes (Folder 6, Box 1)
  - The Affair- Prompt Script (Folder 7, Box 1)
  - Safety and Accident Reports- Anarchist (Folder 8, Box 1)
  - Anarchist- Rehearsal Schedule (Folder 9, Box 1)
  - Anarchist- Prelim Plots (Folder 10, Box 1)
  - After the Fall- Hong Kong (Folder 1-3, Box 2)
  - After the Fall- Arena (Folder 4-6, Box 2)
  - Ah, Wilderness! (Folder 1-2, Box 3)
  - Alice in Wonderland (Folder 3, Box 3)
  - All the King's Men (Folder 4-6, Box 3)
  - All the King's Men (Folder 1-3, Box 4)
  - All The Way Home (Folder 4, Box 4)
  - American Buffalo (Folder 5, Box 4)
  - The American Dream (Folder 1, Box 5)
  - American Splendor (Folder 2-4, Box 5)
  - An American Tragedy (Folder 5, Box 5)
  - An American Tragedy (Folder 1-5, Box 6)
  - The Andersonville Trial (Folder 1-2, Box 7)
  - Animal Crackers (Folder 3-6, Box 7)
  - Animal Crackers (Folder 1-2, Box 8)
  - Answered The Flute (Folder 3-6, Box 8)
  - Answered The Flute (Folder 1-2, Box 9)
  - Apollo of Bellac (Folder 3, Box 9)
  - Arms and the Man (Folder 4-7, Box 9)
  - The Ascent of Mount Fuji (Folder 1-4, Box 10)
  - As You Like It (Folder 1-3, Box 11)
  - The Autumn Garden (Folder 4-5, Box 11)
  - Awake and Sing! (Folder 1-2, Box 12)
  - Banjo Dancing (Folder 3, Box 12)
  - Battle Dream (Folder 4-5, Box 12)
  - Battle Dream (Folder 1-2, Box 13)
  - Bedtime Story (Folder 3, Box 13)
  - Beehive (Folder 4, Box 13)
  - Beyond Therapy (Folder 1, Box 14)
  - Billy Bishop Goes to War (Folder 2, Box 14)
  - Blood Knot (Folder 3-5, Box 14)
  - Boccaccio (Folder 1-5, Box 15)
  - Boy Meets Girl (Folder 6, Box 15)
  - Briar Patch (Folder 1-2, Box 16)
  - Brother Rat (Folder 3, Box 16)
  - The Browning Version (Folder 4, Box 16)
  - The Burning of the Lepers (Folder 5-8, Box 16)
  - Buried Child (Folder 1, Box 17)
  - Busy Dyin' (Folder 2-4, Box 17)
  - Cabrona (Folder 5-6, Box 17)
  - The Cage (Folder 1-3, Box 18)
  - Candide (Folder 4-7, Box 18)
  - Casualties (Folder 1-2, Box 19)
  - Catsplay (Folder 3-6, Box 19)
  - The Caucasian Chalk Circle- 1961 (Folder 1-4, Box 20)
  - The Caucasian Chalk Circle- 1977 (Folder 5-6, Box 20)
  - The Caucasian Chalk Circle- 1977 (Folder 1-6, Box 21)
  - Checkmates (Folder 1, Box 22)
  - The Chemmy Circle (Folder 2-4, Box 22)
  - The Cherry Orchard- 1960 (Folder 5, Box 22)
  - The Cherry Orchard- 1970 (Folder 6, Box 22)
  - The Cherry Orchard- 1970 (Folder 1, Box 23)
  - The Cherry Orchard- 1988 (Folder 2-3, Box 23)
  - The Child (Folder 4-5, Box 23)
  - A Chorus of Disapproval (Folder 1-4, Box 24)
  - Clandestine on the Morning Line (Folder 1-2, Box 25)
  - Cloud 9 (Folder 3-5, Box 25)
  - The Cocoanuts (Folder 1-4, Box 26)
  - Cold Storage (Folder 5, Box 26)
  - Comedians (Folder 1-2, Box 27)
  - Conflict of Interest (Folder 3-5, Box 27)
  - The Conquest of the South Pole (Folder 1-2, Box 28)
  - The Country Wife (Folder 3, Box 28)
  - The Cretan Woman (Folder 4, Box 28)
  - Crime and Punishment (Folder 5, Box 28)
  - Crime and Punishment (Folder 1, Box 29)
  - The Crucible- 1967 (Folder 3, Box 29)
  - The Crucible- 1987 (Folder 4-5, Box 29)
  - The Crucible- 1987 (Folder 1, Box 30)
  - The Curse of the Starving Class (Folder 2, Box 30)
  - Cymbeline (Folder 3-4, Box 30)
  - The Dance of Death (Folder 5, Box 30)
  - The Dance of Death (Folder 1, Box 31)
  - Dandelion Wine (Folder 2-4, Box 31)
  - Dark of the Moon- 1948 (Folder 5, Box 31)
  - Dark of the Moon- 1964 (Folder 1-3, Box 32)
  - Death of a Salesman (Folder 4-5, Box 32)
  - The Delectable Judge (Folder 1-4, Box 33)
  - The Desert Dwellers (Folder 5-6, Box 33)
  - Design for Living (Folder 1-2, Box 34)
  - Desire Under The Elms (Folder 3, Box 34)
  - The Devils (Folder 4-5, Box 34)
  - The Devils (Folder 1, Box 35)
  - The Devil's Disciple (Folder 2, Box 35)
  - Disability- 1978 (Folder 3, Box 35)
  - Disability- 1981 (Folder 4, Box 35)
  - Disability- 1981 (Folder 1, Box 36)
  - The Disenchanted (Folder 2, Box 36)
  - The Doctor's Dilemma (Folder 3, Box 36)
  - Don Juan (Folder 4-5, Box 36)
  - Dream Girl (Folder 1, Box 37)
  - Duck Hunting (Folder 2-4, Box 37)
  - The Dybbuk (Folder 1-2, Box 38)
  - Edith Stein (Folder 3-4, Box 38)
  - Edith Stein (Folder 1-6, Box 39)
  - Edith Stein (Folder 1, Box 40)
  - The Egg (Folder 2-3, Box 40)
  - Emigres (Folder 4-5, Box 40)
  - Enchanted Night - The Police (Folder 6, Box 40)
  - Enemies (Folder 1-2, Box 41)
  - Enemy of the People (Folder 3-5, Box 41)
  - Enrico IV- 1964 (Folder 1-3, Box 42)
  - Enrico IV- 1988 (Folder 4-5, Box 42)
  - Enrico IV- 1988 (Folder 1-2, Box 43)
  - Epitaph for George Dillon (Folder 3, Box 43)
  - Execution of Justice (Folder 4-6, Box 43)
  - Exhibition (Folder 1-2, Box 44)
  - The Firebrand (Folder 3, Box 44)
  - Forever Yours, Marie-Lou (Folder 4, Box 44)
  - The Foursome (Folder 5, Box 44)
  - The Front Page- 1958 (Folder 1, Box 45)
  - The Front Page- 1974-75 (Folder 2, Box 45)
  - The Front Page- 1975-76 (Folder 3-4, Box 45)
  - Galileo- 1964-65 (Folder 5, Box 45)
  - Galileo- 1964-65 (Folder 1-3, Box 46)
  - Galileo- 1980 (Folder 4-5, Box 46)
  - The Gang's All Here (Folder 1-2, Box 47)
  - Gemini (Folder 3, Box 47)
  - Geniuses (Folder 4, Box 47)
  - The Girl on the Via Flamina (Folder 5, Box 47)
  - Glengarry Glen Ross (Folder 1, Box 48)
  - God Bless You, Mr. Rosewater (Folder 2-5, Box 48)
  - Golden Boy (Folder 1, Box 49)
  - Good Person of Setzuan (Folder 2-3, Box 49)
  - The Gospel at Colonus (Folder 4-5, Box 49)
  - The Great White Hope (Folder 1-4, Box 50)
  - Hamlet (Folder 1-3, Box 51)
  - Happy End (Folder 4-5, Box 51)
  - Hard Travelin' (Folder 6, Box 51)
  - The Hasty Heart (Folder 1, Box 52)
  - Heartbreak House- 1976 (Folder 2-4, Box 52)
  - Heartbreak House- 1987 (Folder 5-6, Box 52)
  - A History of the American Film (Folder 1-5, Box 53)
  - A History of the American Film (Folder 1, Box 54)
  - Horatio (Folder 2-4, Box 54)
  - The Hostage- 1963 (Folder 5-6, Box 54)
  - The Hostage- 1963 (Folder 1-2, Box 55)
  - The Hostage- 1972 (Folder 3-5, Box 55)
  - Hotel Paradiso (Folder 1, Box 56)
  - The House of Blue Leaves (Folder 2, Box 56)
  - I'm a Woman (Folder 3, Box 56)
  - The Iceman Cometh- 1960 (Folder 4-5, Box 56)
  - The Iceman Cometh- 1968 (Folder 1-3, Box 57)
  - Idiot's Delight (Folder 4-5, Box 57)
  - The Imaginary Invalid (Folder 6, Box 57)
  - The Immigrant (Folder 1-4, Box 58)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest (Folder 5, Box 58)
  - Indians (Folder 6, Box 58)
  - Indians (Folder 1-2, Box 59)
  - Inherit the Wind (Folder 3-5, Box 59)
  - Inherit the Wind (Folder 1-3, Box 60)
  - The Inspector General- 1951 (Folder 4, Box 60)
  - The Inspector General- 1967 (Folder 5, Box 60)
  - The Inspector General- 1967 (Folder 1-2, Box 61)
  - The Island, Sizwe Bansi is Dead (Folder 3, Box 61)
  - Isn't it Romantic? (Folder 4-5, Box 61)
  - Joe Turner's Come and Gone (Folder 6, Box 61)
  - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris (Folder 1, Box 62)
  - Judevine (Folder 2, Box 62)
  - Julius Caesar- 1951 (Folder 3-4, Box 62)
  - Julius Caesar- 1974-75 (Folder 5-6, Box 62)
  - Julius Caesar- 1974-75 (Folder 1, Box 63)
  - Juno and the Peacock- 1958 (Folder 2, Box 63)
  - Juno and the Peacock- 1990 (Folder 3,4, Box 63)
  - Kean (Folder 5-6, Box 63)
  - King Lear (Folder 1-3, Box 64)
  - K2 (Folder 4, Box 64)
  - Ladder to the Moon (Folder 5, Box 64)
  - The Lady's not for Burning (Folder 6, Box 64)
  - The Last Meeting of the Knights of the White Magnolia (Folder 1, Box 65)
  - Leonce and Lena (Folder 2-3, Box 65)
  - Les Blancs (Folder 4-5, Box 65)
  - The Lesson (Folder 1, Box 66)
  - A Lesson From Aloes (Folder 2, Box 66)
  - A Lie of the Mind (Folder 3-5, Box 66)
  - Light up the Sky (Folder 1-3, Box 67)
  - Living at Home (Folder 4-6, Box 67)
  - Living at Home (Folder 1-2, Box 68)
  - The Lonesome Train (Folder 3, Box 68)
  - A Long Day's Journey Into Night- 1965 (Folder 4-5, Box 68)
  - Long Day's Journey Into Night- 1975 (Folder 1-3, Box 69)
  - A Look at the Fifties (Folder 4, Box 69)
  - A Look at the Fifties (Folder 1-3, Box 70)
  - Look Back in Anger (Folder 4, Box 70)
  - Loose Ends (Folder 5, Box 70)
  - Loose Ends (Folder 1, Box 71)
  - The Lower Depths (Folder 2-4, Box 71)
  - Macbeth (Folder 5-6, Box 71)
  - Mademoiselle Colombe (Folder 1-2, Box 72)
  - Madmen (Folder 3-5, Box 72)
  - Madmen (Folder 1, Box 73)
  - The Madwoman of Chaillot (Folder 2, Box 73)
  - The Magistrate (Folder 3-6, Box 73)
  - Major Barbara- 1959-60 (Folder 7, Box 73)